(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
The night shines brighter when she sings...
Special guests are here to join the fun
so don't blink
The moment we've all been waiting for...
あぁ、ふわふわ...
Ah, fluff fluff...
こんなことにな
I never thought
るなんて
it would happen
出会う前にわかってたら
If only I knew before we met
もう少しだけシャンとした僕を
I could have shown you a cooler side of me
見せれたはずなんだ
I'm sure I could have
どうしたらいいのかなんて
What should I do?
頭ではわかってるけど
I know it in my head, but
何気ないちょっとした言葉で
Just from your casual words
わぁ、おっ、おっ
Wah, oh, oh
嬉しい顔が出ちゃって
A happy face just slips out
こんなバレバレじゃカッコ悪いな
It's so uncool to be this obvious
けどこのままじゃ引き下がれないよな
But I can't back down now
でも今更カッコつけて照れくさくて
But now it's embarrassing to try and look cool
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I can't say that I like you
この気持ち伝わるかな
Will these feelings reach you?
浮き足立って空回り
I'm restless and spinning my wheels
何も言えずまたさよなら
Saying goodbye again without saying anything
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I like you so much it's unbearable
明日こそは言えるかな
Will I be able to say it tomorrow?
あなたも僕に同じように
If you felt the same way about me
恋してたら
If you were in love
なんて考えちゃうんだ
That's what I end up thinking
会えない日が続いてる
Days without seeing you continue
このままじゃよろしくない
This isn't good
会ったところで何ができるって
Not that I can do anything if we meet
わけじゃないんだけど
It's not like that, but
こんな恋は二度とないな
I'll never have a love like this again
頭ではわかってるけど
I know it in my head, but
眩しすぎその笑顔が
That smile is too bright
わぁ、おっ、おっ
Wah, oh, oh
僕を焦らせるんだ
It makes me panic
ずっと見ていたくなるような
I want to keep watching you forever
独り占めしたくなってしまうよな
I start wanting to have you all to myself
こんな気持ちわかるのかな
Do you understand these feelings?
あなたが笑ってるならそれでいいんです
If you are smiling, then that's enough
でも隣は僕がいいな
But I wish I was the one next to you
もしかしたら実は
Maybe, actually
ずっと気づいてる
You've noticed all along
じゃないかな
Haven't you?
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I like you so much it's unbearable
手をひっくり返すくらいの
Like turning over a hand,
粋なセリフは
such a witty line...
言えそうにないや
I don't think I can say.
どうしたってこの気持ちは
No matter what, these feelings...
抑えられそうにはないんだ
cannot be suppressed.
あなたと出会ったあの日から
Since the day I met you,
ずっと気持ちは変わらないけど
my feelings haven't changed, but...
あなたのことが好きだなんて言えないんです
I can't say that I love you.
この気持ち伝わるかな
Will these feelings reach you?
浮き足立って空回り
Restless and spinning in circles,
何も言えずまたサヨナラ
saying nothing, and it's goodbye again.
あなたのことが好きすぎてたまらないんです
I love you so much it's unbearable.
明日こそは言いたいな
I want to say it tomorrow for sure.
あなたも僕に同じように
If you also felt the same way about me...
恋してたら
...and fell in love,
なんて考えてる
...I'm thinking about things like that.
でも分かってる
But I know,
考えすぎってこと
I'm just overthinking it.
Oh, oh, oh...
Bokobokobo, Kobo Kanaeru at your service! Let me be your sun to shine your day!
Ehehe...
Hi everyone! こんばんは！
Hi everyone! Good evening!
コボ・カナエルです！
I am Kobo Kanaeru!
コボの3Dバースデー配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
Welcome to Kobo Kanaeru 3D birthday stream 2025!
パチパチパチ！
Clap clap clap!
How was Kobo's performance?
どうだった？
How was it?
またギターで出てきたよね。えへへ。
I came out with a guitar again, huh? Ehehe.
え、ちょっと待って。
Eh, wait a moment.
Let me put the guitar down first.
(よいしょ、よいしょ... うにょ)
(Grunts)
Okay... Whew.
Once again, welcome to Kobo's 3D Birthday Stream 2025!
コボの3D生誕配信へようこそ！
Welcome to Kobo's 3D birthday stream!
This time, I, Kobo, will be hosting an... um...
idolみたい concert...
idol-like concert...
themed 3D birthday stream for about an hour...
with a lot of amazing and awesome guests!
I bet you guys can't wait!
"Hei Kobo! Oi! Is your stage different?"
"Hey Kobo! Oi! Is your stage different?"
Ah! Chat! Nice... Nice eyes chat! You noticed it!
Yeah you're right! Look at Kobo's new stage!
わぁ！デカい！
Wah! Huge!
新しいステージや！
It's a new stage!
There's a big Cilus right here.
Cilus... 大きなCilus。
Cilus... big Cilus.
うにょ、うにょ、うにょ...
Squish, squish, squish...
And so many stars! Stars!
So many stars!
And then... a big... a big rainbow right here!
Big, very big rainbow.
And so many clouds because... um... I don't know,
I think it's just very aesthetic.
And the floor! Floor!
Floor 見てて！
Look at the floor!
わぁ... なんか... pattern... うん... 海みたい。
Wow... kinda... pattern... yeah... like the sea.
You know? Yeah like my hair.
So, um... Don't forget to take a lot of screenshots, okay?
Especially later. Okay? Get a lot of screenshots.
And then post your comments, your moments, your impressions,
your everything with the hashtag #3DKobornDay2025 on your SNS.
そして、コボの3Dバースデー配信...
And, Kobo's 3D birthday stream...
SNSにハッシュタグ #3DKobornDay2025...
on SNS with hashtag #3DKobornDay2025...
2025... をつけて...
...attach 2025...
...コメントや思い出、感想などなど
...and post comments, memories, impressions etc.
投稿してね！
please post them!
And... right.
Are you guys ready for the next performance?
Okay! Let's go to the next performance!
Wait, I tried to...
あ、オッケー。
Ah, okay.
入ってます。
It's on.
それでは皆さん、準備いいか？
Well then everyone, are you ready?
Let's go to the next song.
とくべつチューして
Give me a special kiss.
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" isn't enough.
一番大事がいい
I want to be your number one.
君が作るオリジナルの
With an original style made just by you,
とくべつチューして
Give me a special kiss.
眩しくて目が覚めて
So bright it wakes me up,
愛しく想ってよ
Think of me lovingly.
眠り姫のように
Like a sleeping beauty,
優しく口づけて
Kiss me gently.
夢見たこの世界
In this world I dreamed of,
魔法がかかる君がいる
There is magic, because you are here.
全てに触れずに
Without touching everything,
二人だけで You & I
Just the two of us, You & I.
私のこと
Make me...
独占して
...yours exclusively.
君だけのものになってもいい
I don't mind becoming yours alone.
なんでもある日の
On a day with everything,
なんでもない
Or on a day with nothing,
気づいてね
Please notice me.
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" isn't enough.
君の特別にして
Make me your special one.
ねぇもっと Give me a kiss more 私は
Hey, give me a kiss more, I am...
君でいっぱいよ
...full of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
Like a ribbon knot that won't come undone,
小指キュって縛って
Tie our pinkies tight.
そうよ一生、一生涯も
Yes, for a lifetime, my whole life,
特別が欲しい
I want something special.
二人きり週末は
On weekends just for the two of us,
奏でてよハーモニー
Play a harmony for me.
目が星見たら
When our eyes meet the stars,
私を想ってほしい
I want you to think of me.
甘々な君なのに
Even though you're so sweet,
広い街 吸い込まれ
Swallowed up by the wide city.
戦う姿に
For your fighting figure,
大きい花丸だね
I give you a big flower mark.
好きなとこ 優しいとこ
Parts I like, gentle parts,
嫌いなとこも 優しいとこ
Even parts I hate, are gentle parts.
誰にもあげない
I won't give you to anyone,
私だけ独り占め
I'll keep you all to myself.
うだって 今までの人と
After all, I don't need the same thing...
同じはいらないんです
...as all the people before.
ねぇもっと Give me a love 私のため
Hey, give me more love, just for me.
生きてほしいんです
I want you to live for me.
だからウサギと私は
So, the rabbit and I,
寂しくさせないで
Don't make us lonely.
そんなんじゃ束縛じゃないわ
That's not being possessive,
苦しいのが好き
I like it when it hurts.
ショートケーキ
Shortcake,
苺みたいに座ってもいい？
Can I sit there like a strawberry?
赤く甘い恋だもん
It's a red, sweet love.
食べ上げた
I ate it all up.
大好きも
My love too,
返してもらって全部私に
Give it all back to me,
頂戴
Give it to me.
もっと！
More!
君は神様が作る
You are like a miracle...
奇跡のような人
...created by God.
擦れた今日も その寝顔も
Even this worn-out day, and that sleeping face,
守ってあげるね
I'll protect them for you.
Yeah
Oh baby I love you じゃ足りない
Oh baby, "I love you" isn't enough.
君の特別にして
Make me your special one.
ねぇもっと Give me a kiss more 私は
Hey, give me a kiss more, I am...
君でいっぱいよ
...full of you.
ほどけないリボン結び
Like a ribbon knot that won't come undone,
小指キュって縛って
Tie our pinkies tight.
ねぇ Baby 最初で最後の
Hey baby, make me your first and last...
特別にしてね
...special one.
ワハハハ！
Wahahaha!
天天天天天天天
Ten ten ten ten ten ten ten!
Go Go Go Go Go Go! Open sesame!
闇と光の交わるファナティック
A fanatic where darkness and light intersect.
今宵味わうサイケデリック
Taste the psychedelic tonight.
踊り絡まり合うゾディアック
Dancing and intertwining Zodiac.
恋の駆け引きのタイブレイク
A tie-break in the game of love.
計らない存在
An immeasurable existence,
形を引きたい
I want to draw its shape.
夢見た心地 触れ合い惑わせたい
A dreamy feeling, I want to touch and bewilder you.
曖昧
Ambiguous.
解けない
Unsolvable.
見つめ合って...
Staring at each other...
限界
Limit.
月夜に誘われ
Invited by the moonlit night,
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a devil,
悪魔が悪魔が
The devil, the devil,
あまさず化成した
Transformation without leaving anything out.
天国 地獄の
Heaven, Hell's...
狭間で出会った
Met in the rift.
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a devil,
悪魔が集って踊れば
If devils gather and dance,
天国 地獄の
Heaven, Hell's...
門が開く
Gate opens.
闇と光の交わる fanatic
Darkness and light intersecting, fanatic.
今宵味わう psychedelic
Tonight tasting psychedelic.
踊り絡まり合う zodiac
Dancing entangling zodiac.
恋の駆け引きの tie break
Love's tactics tie break.
Dead, Alive
Dead, Dead, Dead
Buzz, Buzz, Buzz
Dead, Alive
Dead, Dead
Buzz, Buzz
Dead!
Buzz!
Let's Go!
生きた魂を取りにおいて
Taking the living soul aside,
巡る運命のカード 揺れる炎
Rotating destiny's card, swaying flame.
先にあなたが kiss したら
If you kiss first,
もう迷わない plus 飲み干して
No longer hesitating, plus drink it up.
今宵 all in 降りない
Tonight all in, not folding,
賭の勝負
In this gambling match.
今 天国と地獄を繋ぐ門が開く
Now the gate connecting heaven and hell opens.
天使と悪魔
Angel and devil,
死者と生者が入り乱れ
The dead and the living jumbled together,
踊り笑い
Dancing, laughing,
全ては混沌の中に飲み込まれていく
Everything gets swallowed into chaos.
それは世界の終焉であり
That is the end of the world,
新たなる始まりでもあるのだった
And it was also a new beginning.
Dead, Alive
Dead, Dead, Dead
Buzz, Buzz, Buzz
Dead, Alive
Dead, Dead
Buzz, Buzz
Dead!
Buzz!
Bang!
天国 天
Heaven, Hea...
Bang! Bang!
天国 地獄
Heaven, Hell.
Bang! Bang!
天国 天
Heaven, Hea...
Bang! Bang!
天国 地獄
Heaven, Hell.
月夜に誘われ
Invited by the moonlit night,
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a devil,
悪魔が悪魔が
The devil, the devil,
あまさず化成した
Transformation without leaving anything out.
天国 地獄の
Heaven, Hell's...
恍惚 消えない
Ecstasy won't disappear,
果てない 問題
Endless problem.
天国 地獄の
Heaven, Hell's...
狭間で出会った
Met in the rift.
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a devil,
悪魔が集って踊れば
If devils gather and dance,
天国 地獄の
Heaven, Hell's...
狭間で出会った
Met in the rift.
天使と悪魔と
With an angel and a devil,
悪魔が集って踊れば
If devils gather and dance,
Dance! Dance!
Dead! Alive!
天国 Alive!
Heaven, Alive!
Dead! Dead!
天国 地獄
Heaven, Hell.
Dead! Alive!
天国 Alive!
Heaven, Alive!
Bang! Bang!
天国 地獄
Heaven, Hell.
Cool!
弱い！
Weak!
Iblis dari manakah?
Where is this devil from?
我が... 天... Orang Iblis... Wa... Wa...
My... Heaven... Devil person... Wa... Wa...
Wahai!
Oh my!
Itu empat tanduk bahaya sebelah sekali.
Those four horns are very dangerous on one side.
Iya jadi gini...
Yeah, so like this...
Aku datang jauh-jauh...
I came from far away...
Apa?
What?
Meskipun tidak diundang...
Even though I wasn't invited...
Oh, diundang!
Oh, you were invited!
Iya kayaknya kamu ngundang yang lain itu tadi.
Yeah, I think you invited someone else just now.
Maksudnya... No you imi?
Meaning... What do you mean?
Kenapa tiba-tiba nunggu?
Why suddenly wait?
Kamu malaikat Jepang ya?
Are you a Japanese angel?
Bisa berhenti muter? Ngepusing.
Can you stop spinning? It's dizzying.
Pusing, ya udah.
Dizzy, okay then.
Malaikat kok pusing guys.
An angel getting dizzy, guys.
Iya aku di sini soalnya...
Yeah, I'm here because...
Datang buat ngerayu kamu aja sebenarnya.
I actually came just to seduce you.
Pengen main bareng.
Wanted to play together.
Pengen godain kamu aja.
Just wanted to tease you.
Eh? Apa sih? Apa sih? Ih... Malu...
Eh? What is it? What? Ih... Embarrassed...
Sini, sini, sini, sini.
Come here, here, here, here.
Ada cinta...
There is love...
Pulang, kamu habis ini... loh...
Go home, you after this... loh...
Kamu habis ini pulang sama aku kan?
You're going home with me after this, right?
Pulang.
Going home.
Iya.
Yes.
Habis ini gak ada apa-apa lagi kan?
After this there's nothing else right?
Ngapain enak-enak aku di atas.
Why would I, it's nice for me up above.
Masa kamu mau seret ke bawah?
You want to drag me down?
Loh, kita... loh... Bukannya kita...
Loh, we... loh... Aren't we...
Kita, kita!
We, we!
Gua aja iblis.
I'm the only devil.
Ajak dong... ajak dong bang.
Invite me... invite me, bro.
Kamu saya ajak.
I invite you.
Aku kesepian.
I'm lonely.
Ayo sini.
Come here.
Bareng ya.
Together, okay.
Fallen Angel nih.
Fallen Angel here.
Enggak, enggak ada Fallen Angel.
No, there is no Fallen Angel.
Musik nih, sini aku panah.
Music, let me shoot you here.
Iya iya coba coba.
Yeah yeah, try it.
Panah asmara.
Arrow of love.
Satu, dua, tiga.
One, two, three.
Wah gila, gila.
Wow crazy, crazy.
How to tame your demon.
Atas.
Top.
Bawah.
Bottom.
Atas.
Top.
Terus tapi pas kamu atas, aku bawah.
But then when you're on top, I'm on the bottom.
Kebalik.
It's reversed.
Tau ya, orang mah kebalik kiri kanan.
You know, people usually mix up left and right.
Dia kebalik atas bawah.
She mixes up up and down.
Atas!
Top!
Aku bawah.
I'm bottom.
Atas!
Top!
Kocak, kocak. Ya udah.
Funny, funny. Alright then.
Ya udah kalo gitu, aku... aku wanita sibuk ya sebenernya.
Alright then, I... I'm actually a busy woman.
Jadi kayak emang ga ada... ga gitu banyak waktu, aku disini mampir...
So like there really isn't... not that much time, I just stopped by here...
Buset.
Wow.
Mampir dikit aja bentaran.
Just stopping by for a little bit.
Kasih 5 detik buat kamu.
I'll give you 5 seconds.
Pemimpin di Guild nih.
Guild Leader, huh.
Asik!
Cool!
Oke.
Okay.
Baik.
Good.
Fiksi ya guys. Ini cerita fiksi jangan ditiru adegan-adegan...
This is fiction, guys. This is a fictional story, don't imitate these scenes...
Sensitif ini, sensitif.
This is sensitive, sensitive.
Fiksi ya... boongan.
Fiction, okay... it's fake.
Oke kalo gitu, bye!
Okay then, bye!
Engga mau ikut aku lagi...
She doesn't want to follow me anymore...
Bye bye bye bye!
Jagain nih anak ya guys. Kita lihat perilakunya. Beneran seiso atau enggak.
Look after this kid, guys. Let's watch her behavior. Truly seiso or not.
Liat tuh, liat tuh bajunya. Jagain, jagain.
Look at that, look at that outfit. Watch her, watch her.
Ya udah, bye!
Alright then, bye!
Bisa jadi Fallen Angel aku karena hasutan dia, guys.
I might become a Fallen Angel because of her influence, guys.
Panas.
So hot.
ドキドキキュン！
Dokidoki Kyun!
送るラブビーム
Sending a Love Beam.
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
The taste of love that makes you crazy.
何とかしなくちゃならなくて
I had to do something,
突然メイドになっちゃって
And suddenly I became a maid!
いつものようにお店の掃除
Cleaning the shop just like always,
トビラ開いちゃって目が合った
The door opened and our eyes met.
なんだか忙しくなっちゃって
Somehow it got really busy,
あわてんぼうにもなっちゃって
And I became a scatterbrain too.
お仕事中に！
While working!
推しに夢中に！
Crazy about my fave!
どこを探しても見当たらないじゃん
I can't find you anywhere I look!
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って
Wait a moment!
もういいよ！
I'm ready!
秘密だよね？
It's a secret, right?
もういいの？
Is it okay now?
好きになっちゃって
I've fallen for you,
ねえ
Hey...
好きって言って！
Say you love me!
ドキドキキュン！送るラブビーム
Dokidoki Kyun! Sending a Love Beam.
君を夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that makes you crazy.
ほらドキドキキュン！わたし大暴走
Look, Dokidoki Kyun! I'm going wild.
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
The taste of love that makes you crazy.
もう君にキュン！わたし大妄想
Already Kyun for you! My huge delusion.
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic that lets me be crazy with you.
だから君がキュン！ってなる恋になって
So fall in a love that makes you go Kyun!
一つどうぞこれが恋の味
Here's one for you, this is the taste of love!
楽しくて仕方なくたって
Even if it's so fun I can't help it,
そろそろ終わりになっちゃって
It's starting to come to an end.
会いたくなって落ち込んじゃって
I wanted to see you and got depressed,
君とぶつかって目が合った
Then I bumped into you and our eyes met!
何度も会いたくなっちゃって
I wanted to see you again and again,
今日だけじゃ足りないんだって
Today alone isn't enough!
計画通り！
Just as planned!
わたしの勝利！
My victory!
君に会いたくて仕方がないよ
I can't help wanting to see you so much.
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って
Wait a moment!
もういいの？
Is it okay now?
君だけだよ！
It's only you!
もうずっと！
Forever more!
愛し合いたいよ... ね
I want us to love each other... right?
好きって言って！
Say you love me!
ドキドキキュン！君にラブビーム
Dokidoki Kyun! A Love Beam for you.
二人夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic that makes us both crazy.
ほらドキドキキュン！わたし大恋愛
Look, Dokidoki Kyun! My passionate love.
君も夢中にさせる恋の魔鬼
The love scroll that makes you crazy too.
もう君にキュン！わたし大混乱
Already Kyun for you! I'm in huge chaos.
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic that lets me be crazy with you.
だから君はキュン！ってなる恋に落ちて
So fall in a love that makes you go Kyun!
一つどうぞこれが恋の味
Here's one for you, this is the taste of love!
ああ、このままだったら
Ah, if things stay like this,
ここで会うこともなくなって
We won't even meet here anymore.
もう君の声が
I just want to hear...
聞きたくなるの
...your voice right now.
もういいかい？
Are you ready?
ちょっと待って
Wait a moment!
もういいの？
Is it okay now?
秘密だもの
Because it's a secret.
もういいよ！
I'm ready!
このまま好きになってく
I'll keep falling in love like this.
好きって言って！
Say you love me!
ドキドキキュン！送るラブビーム
Dokidoki Kyun! Sending a Love Beam.
君を夢中にさせる魔法じゃん
It's a magic that makes you crazy.
ほらドキドキキュン！わたし大暴走
Look, Dokidoki Kyun! I'm going wild.
君を夢中にさせる恋の味
The taste of love that makes you crazy.
もう君にキュン！わたし大妄想
Already Kyun for you! My huge delusion.
君と夢中になれる魔法じゃん
It's magic that lets me be crazy with you.
だから君がキュン！ってなる恋になって
So fall in a love that makes you go Kyun!
一つどうぞこれが恋の味
Here's one for you, this is the taste of love!
Halo semuanya!
Hello everyone!
Hehe. Langit udah mulai gelap tapi...
Hehe. The sky has started to get dark but...
Masih pada semangat gak semuanya?
Is everyone still excited?
んーと…
Umm...
次は、こぼはまた一人で歌いたいなと思います。
Next, Kobo would like to sing alone again.
これから歌うこの曲は
The song I'm going to sing now...
最近こぼが気に入っている曲で
...is one that Kobo has really liked recently.
聴いたら幸せな気持ちになりました。
Listening to it made me feel happy.
皆さんも
Everyone too...
この曲聴いて
...please listen to this song...
幸せを感じてくれたら嬉しいです。
...and I'd be glad if you could feel the happiness.
それでは
So then...
次の曲
...the next song is...
青山テルマさんの
...Aoyama Thelma-san's...
「Happiness」です！
..."Happiness"!
きっと Happiness
Surely, happiness
君がいれば
As long as you are here
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくても
Even if you don't say anything
感じてるよ You're the one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me
Oh oh oh...
You always make me happy
落ち込んで眠れなくて
Feeling down and unable to sleep
君との写真 見つめている
I stare at the photos of you and me
いくつもの笑顔たちに
By your many smiles
助けられるよ My life
I am saved, my life
ずっと一緒だよ
We'll be together forever
泣いてもいいよ
It's okay to cry
あの涙を抱きしめてくれた
You embraced those tears of mine
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ここにいるから
I'm right here
すぐに会いたいって
I want to see you right now
きっと Happiness
Surely, happiness
君がいれば
As long as you are here
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくても
Even if you don't say anything
感じてるよ You're the one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me
君と Happiness
Happiness with you
どんな時も
No matter when
一人じゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that I'm not alone
涙あふれたって
Even if my tears overflow
歩けるね Please stay by my side
I can keep walking, please stay by my side
君に出会えてからは
Since I met you
素直に笑っていられるよ
I've been able to smile honestly
少しずつ自分のこと
Little by little, my own self...
好きになった For your love
...I came to like, for your love
そう 今なら
Yes, if it's now
ねえ 心から
Hey, from the bottom of my heart
分かり合えるって思えるよ
I feel like we can understand each other
強がらずに
Without acting tough
ありのままでも
Even just as I am
見つめてくれた
You watched over me
だから Happiness
So, happiness
君のことも
Everything about you...
今よりももっと知りたくて
...I want to know even more than now
どんな言葉よりも
More than any words
大切なの You're the one for me
You are precious, you're the one for me
私も君に何か
I also want to do something for you
できることしたいよ
I want to do whatever I can
いつでも一緒だから
Because we're together anytime
守ってゆけるから
I can protect you
ずっと...
Forever...
きっと Happiness
Surely, happiness
君がいれば
As long as you are here
大丈夫だって思えるよ
I feel like everything will be alright
何も言わなくても
Even if you don't say anything
感じてるよ You're the one for me
I can feel it, you're the one for me
君と Happiness
Happiness with you
どんな時も
No matter when
一人じゃないって信じてるよ
I believe that I'm not alone
涙あふれたって
Even if my tears overflow
歩けるね Please stay by my side
I can keep walking, please stay by my side
大切な You're the one for me
My precious, you're the one for me
Hehe. Let's Go!
Oh oh oh...
You always make me happy
Smile for me baby
Lalala...
You always make me happy
Smile for me baby
Oh oh oh...
You always make me happy
ようこそおいでなさったご主人様
Welcome, my Master.
隣座ってせーの
Sit next to me, ready, set...
萌え萌え萌え萌え
Moe moe moe moe!
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who would be happy with something like this?
ねえ教えて 笑顔であっぷっぷ
Hey, tell me, with a smile, appu-ppu.
愛想忘れてご苦労様
Forgetting your amiability, thank you for your hard work.
私とあなたでせーの
You and I, ready, set...
LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE
こんなんで誰が喜ぶのさ
Who would be happy with something like this?
ねえ教えて 笑顔であっぷっぷ
Hey, tell me, with a smile, appu-ppu.
ヒラリハラリ 女の子
Fluttering, floating, a girl.
フワリフワリ 言葉の相
Drifting, drifting, the aspect of words.
それつまりお冷の
That means, in short, like cold water...
感情的である笑顔であっぷっぷ
...being emotional, with a smile, appu-ppu.
人は見かけによらぬもの
People are not what they seem.
嘘嘘だと見抜けない
You can't see through the lies as lies.
したたかなそうで漫ろなかい
Looking tough, are you restless?
トリハラサミハラ アン・ドゥ・トア
Torihara Samihara Un Deux Trois.
間違ったご指名をいただきまさ
I've received the wrong nomination.
私とあなたでせーの
You and I, ready, set...
LOVE LOVE LOVE LOVE
これはド派手にご苦労様
This is flashily, thank you for your hard work.
遊びましょ 笑顔であっぷっぷ
Let's play, with a smile, appu-ppu.
ヒラリハラリ ここはどこ
Fluttering, floating, where is this?
フワリフワリ 外は雨でしょ
Drifting, drifting, it's raining outside, right?
それつまりお冷の
That means, in short, like cold water...
感情的である笑顔であっぷっぷ
...being emotional, with a smile, appu-ppu.
歌い出す秘密の鐘
The secret bell starts to sing,
終わることのないこの世界
in this world that never ends.
悲しい子供は
The sad children,
虚しい子供は
the empty children,
眠らせて
let them sleep.
おままごと 遊びましょ 笑顔であっぷっぷ
Playing house, let's play, with a smile, appu-ppu.
ヒラリハラリ 女の子
Fluttering, floating, a girl.
フワリフワリ 言葉の相
Drifting, drifting, the aspect of words.
それつまりお冷の
That means, in short, like cold water...
感情的である笑顔であっぷっぷ
...being emotional, with a smile, appu-ppu.
遊びましょ 笑顔であっぷっぷ
Let's play, with a smile, appu-ppu.
あっぷっぷ
Appu-ppu.
Let's dance with me
Sunday Night Magic
何回でもできる True Magic
True Magic that we can do again and again.
まだまだ今日は夢見心地
Today is still feeling like a dream.
止められなくても我慢できない
Even if I can't stop it, I can't hold back.
朝が来るその時まで
Until the moment morning comes.
僕とどうだい
How about with me?
塞ぎ込んでる週の終わりに
At the end of a depressing week,
退屈そうだけどどうだろう
it looks boring, but what do you think?
誘っていいかな
Can I invite you?
構わない 構わない かも分かんない
I don't mind, I don't mind, maybe I don't know.
どっち向いてる こっち向いてる
Which way are you looking? You're looking this way.
あっち向いてはなんかじゃなくて
It's not about looking that way or anything.
君のことだもん
Because it's about you.
もっとちゃんと話聞いてよ
Listen to me more properly!
Hey, Let's seek a lucky happy turn
昨日より今日の方が可愛いし
Because today is cuter than yesterday.
居ても立ってもいられない
I can't just sit still.
聞こえるZeroの告げるチャイム
I can hear the chime announcing Zero.
時間切れの先へ
To the point beyond time running out.
飛び出して駆け出して
Jump out, run out,
まだまだ夜終われない
the night can't end yet.
そんな最高な日々が
If such best days...
明日も続いてくなら
...continue on to tomorrow too,
ねえ君もどうだい
hey, how about you too?
待ち望んでる君の理想の
The ideal you've been waiting for,
お姫様の席をどうしよう
what should I do with the princess's seat?
狙っていいかな
Can I aim for it?
Make chance, Last dance, え？今じゃない？
Make chance, Last dance, eh? Not now?
猫も杓子も曲に合わせて
Everyone and anyone, matching the song,
ステップなんか踏んでみて
try stepping or something.
ご機嫌そう
You look in a good mood.
昨日より今日がずっと楽しくて
Today is much more fun than yesterday.
続けたい時には
When you want to keep going,
聞こえるZeroの告げるチャイム
I can hear the chime announcing Zero.
時間切れの先へ
To the point beyond time running out.
終わらない止まらない
It won't end, it won't stop,
まだまだ夜長いから
because the night is still long.
This is my club, cause it's flawless.
騒がしくて馬鹿らしいよなんて 笑い合える毎日がいい
I prefer days where we can laugh about how noisy and silly things are.
魔法なんてあり得ない でも今宵だけは現実になるかも
Magic is impossible, but maybe just for tonight, it'll become reality.
One, two, three, four!
音に乗って踊れ 君も
Ride the sound and dance, you too!
終わらない夜に とびきりの魔法
In this never-ending night, an extraordinary magic,
君にもかけてあげるから
I'll cast it on you too.
僕の手を取ってよ
So take my hand.
聞こえる鳴り止まない Music
Can you hear it? The music that won't stop ringing.
魔法が解けるまで
Until the magic spell breaks.
最高で最強な夜が 今日も更けていく
The best and strongest night is getting late again.
こんな夢みたいな日々が 明日も続いてくなら
If these dream-like days could just continue tomorrow...
ねえ 君はどうだい？
Hey, how about you?
アンコール 大胆に夜を飾る Songs
Encore! Songs that boldly decorate the night.
何回でもかける Chu Magic
I'll cast this Kiss Magic as many times as you want.
まだまだ Two of you make a good party
Not yet, two of you make a good party!
嘘みたいだけど
It feels like a lie, but...
朝が来るその時まで
Until the moment morning comes.
ねえ 僕とどうだい？
Hey, won't you join me?
うわっ！うわ～！
Whoa! Whaa~!
ここ... ここはどこ？
Where... Where is this?
分かんない。
I dunno.
え、なんか雲おいしそうじゃない？
Eh, don't the clouds look yummy?
食べてみなよ。
Try eating it.
あ～ん... (パクッ)
Aahn... (Chomp)
うわっ、超おいちい！
Whoa, super tasty!
おいしい！？
Tasty!?
あちゃちゃ... 何... あちゃ...
Ah-cha-cha... What... Ah-cha...
何がしてるの！？
What are you doing!?
食べちゃった！食べちゃった！
She ate it! She ate it!
食べちゃうよ！
I'm gonna eat it!
あ、初は食べてないです。
Ah, Hajime didn't eat any.
う～、私の雲～！
Ugh, my clouuud!
見守ってた、見守ってた。
I was watching, just watching!
誰が？奏？
Who? Kanade?
う～ん... 初は食べてないです。
Umm... Hajime didn't eat any.
だ、誰が...
Wh-who did...
奏どうえ？
Kanade, how was it?
ちゃちゃ、食べ...
Cha-cha, eat...
う～じゃないんだよ！
Don't give me that 'Uuu'!
何をしてるの？
What are you doing?
Oh, Kobo! Today is your birthday!
Yeah, true!
誕生日！
Birthday!
Happy Birthday!
おめでとう！
Congratulations!
あ、ありがとう！
Ah, thank you!
Yay! Yay!
You are 3 years old!
３歳じゃない！
I'm not 3 years old!
３歳！
3 years old!
イエイ イエイ！
Yay yay!
じゃあ、こぼ先輩と一緒に歌って踊りたい！
So, we want to sing and dance with Kobo-senpai!
歌って踊りたい？
Want to sing and dance?
Dancing Singing?
Okay, okay, okay.
こぼ... 振り付け。
Kobo... choreography.
うわ～！
Woah~!
こぼの振り付け？ Very nice.
Kobo's choreography? Very nice.
「こぼ先生」と呼んでください。
Please call me "Kobo-sensei".
こぼちゃん！こぼちゃん！
Kobo-chan! Kobo-chan!
ああ！ガキとか言わないで！
Aah! Don't call me a brat!
ガキやん！
You ARE a brat!
ガキや！ガキや！
Brat! Brat!
う～ん... (うぅ～)
Mmm... (Ugh...)
じゃあ、勉強した？
So, did you study (the moves)?
もちろん！
Of course!
あ、One two こぼちゃん先輩...
Ah, one two Kobo-chan senpai...
Cho- choreo-graphy, yeah.
Choreography!
じゃあ、行きましょ！
Then, let's go!
Hey!
行きましょ！ OK！
Let's go! OK!
Let's go!
お～、いいん？
Oh, is it good?
ポジション OK！
Position OK!
OK！
OK!
ポジション OK！
Position OK!
誰もいなくなった
Now that everyone has gone,
二人だけの街に
In this town with just us two.
仕掛けだらけの時計が
The clock full of intricate tricks,
夜の訪れ知らせる
Signals the arrival of the night.
夕闇が空を
The twilight dyes the sky,
ワイン色に染めて
In the color of wine.
哀れな二人を
Inviting the pitiful pair,
舞台へと誘う
To the stage.
Just a waltz, a natural tone
あなたに魔法をかける
I will cast a magic spell on you.
Shall we dance a waltz away?
その名前は Honey Me
That name is Honey Me.
蜜月アン・ドゥ・トロワ
Honeymoon Un Deux Trois,
互いの指を絡めて
Entwining each other's fingers.
Chain and whisk a natural turn
あなたに魔法をかける
I'll cast a magic spell on you.
Throw away and over sway
魅惑の蜜 Honey me
Captivating nectar, honey, me.
蜜月 Un Deux Trois
Honeymoon, one, two, three.
その唇を重ねて
Layer those lips on mine.
Singing swinging sweetest song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing the melody of our love.
月明かりが路地を
The moonlight illuminates the alley,
黄金色に照らして
Lighting it up in gold.
幼い二人は
The young couple,
つまずきながら踊る
Dance while stumbling.
蜜月 Un Deux Trois
Honeymoon, one, two, three.
その唇を重ねて
Layer those lips on mine.
Singing swinging sweetest song
二人の夢を奏でる
Playing the melody of our dreams.
シャバダバ 蜜月 Un Deux Trois
Shaba-daba honeymoon, one, two, three.
その唇を重ねて
Layer those lips on mine.
Singing swinging sweetest song
二人の愛を奏でる
Playing the melody of our love.
わあ！楽しかった！
Wow! That was fun!
楽しかった！やった！
It was fun! We did it!
ダンス上手！
Good dancing!
You're good at dancing!
なんか...スワン！
It was like... a swan!
こぼ先輩もスワン！
Kobo-senpai was also a swan!
奏スワン！
Kanade swan!
Beautiful swan!
めっちゃエレガント！
So elegant!
エレガントにできた！
We did it elegantly!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
これ...トリマ...
This... anyway...
AIだよ！
It's AI!
簡単です！簡単だよ！
It's easy! So easy!
楽しかったー！
That was fun!
来てくれてありがとね
Thanks for coming.
呼んでくれてありがチョー！
Thanks for inviting us-cho!
ありがと、こぼ先輩！
Thank you, Kobo-senpai!
一緒に踊ってくれてもありがと
Thanks for dancing with me too.
ジャマジャマ？
Sorry to intrude?
Happy Birthday!
おめでと！
Congratulations!
最後までファイト！
Good luck until the end!
バイバイ！
Bye bye!
みんな帰っちゃった...
Everyone went home...
悲しい...
I'm sad...
誰も来ないのかな...
I wonder if anyone else will come...
さよならの前にキスをして
Kiss me before goodbye.
さよならの後は忘れさせて
Make me forget after goodbye.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name won't disappear.
離れない
Can't leave,
話せない
can't speak,
戻りたい
want to go back.
Take me free
この芳しき...
With this fragrant...
夜中は香水だらけに染めた
Midnight, dyed in perfume,
失恋のフレイバー
the flavor of heartbreak.
当たり前さえも奇跡
Even the ordinary is a miracle.
当たり障りない君との奇跡
A simple, quiet miracle with you.
どれだけ恋しても
No matter how much I love you,
越えられない君を
I can't seem to get over you.
今ならわかる気がして
I feel like I understand now.
今から過去に戻れるなら
If I could go back to the past now...
サヨナラの前に
Before we say goodbye,
キスをして
kiss me.
サヨナラの後は
After the goodbye,
忘れさせて
let me forget.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name just won't disappear.
離れない
Can't leave,
離せない
can't let go,
戻りたい
want to go back.
Take me free
呪いたい
I want to curse you,
ほど愛しているのよ
that's how much I love you.
気づけばあなたのことばかり浮かべて
Before I knew it, I was thinking only of you.
明日になれば
If tomorrow comes,
大丈夫
I'll be okay.
何度言い聞かせればいいの
How many times must I tell myself that?
愛という沼に
In this swamp called love,
溺れてる
I am drowning.
私の声は届かない
My voice doesn't reach you.
サヨナラの前に
Before we say goodbye,
キスをして
kiss me.
サヨナラの後は
After the goodbye,
忘れさせて
let me forget.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name just won't disappear.
離れない
Can't leave,
離せない
can't let go,
戻りたい
want to go back.
Take me free
サヨナラの前に
Before we say goodbye,
キスをして
kiss me.
サヨナラの後は
After the goodbye,
忘れさせて
let me forget.
でもあなたの名前が消えない
But your name just won't disappear.
離れない
Can't leave,
離せない
can't let go,
戻れない
can't go back.
Take me free
closing
帰らない日々
Days that won't return,
抱きしめたまま
while still holding them close.
いつかそう
Someday, yes,
いつか
someday.
弱い心が
Before my weak heart
捕まる前に
gets captured,
そっとあなたを遠ざけた
I softly pushed you away.
ああ こんな気持ち
Ah, this feeling,
辛すぎるよ もう
it's too painful now.
あなたは誰なの
Who are you?
どこに隠れてたの
Where were you hiding?
ひどく怯えてる
Terribly frightened,
うつむいたままの
looking down...
惨めな私が
my miserable self
笑ってた
was laughing.
またあの季節
Again, that season comes.
夜空は白く
The night sky is white.
あなたもいて
You are there too.
触れてこないで
Don't touch me.
嬉しいけど
I'm happy, but...
心が痛い
my heart hurts.
離したくない
I don't want to let go.
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart.
でも諦めてた
But I had given up.
もうこれ以上
I can't fall in love
好きになれない
any more than this.
失う痛み
The pain of loss,
耐えきれないよ
I can't bear it.
帰らない日々
Days that won't return,
抱きしめたまま
while still holding them close.
いつかそう
Someday, yes,
いつか
someday.
ただそばにいて
Just stay by my side,
それだけでいい
that's all I need.
素直にはなれないけれど
Though I can't be honest with my feelings.
さぁ 顔を上げて
Come on, raise your face.
歩み始めなきゃ
I gotta start walking.
リアルな私を気づいて
Notice the real me.
またあの季節 この空の下
Again in that season, under this sky...
見上げている
...I am looking up.
傷ついたもの
The things that were hurt...
もう元には 戻らないけれど
...won't return to how they were, but...
離したくない
I don't want to let go.
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart.
もう諦めない
I won't give up anymore.
あなたの心 傷つけてでも
Even if I hurt your heart...
この気持ちに 嘘はつけない
...I can't lie to this feeling.
いつか笑顔で 話せるような
So that someday we can talk with smiles...
私を見つけて
...find me.
枯れそうにいて
As if withering away...
聞かせてほしい 二度と一人にはしないと
...I want you to tell me that you'll never leave me alone again.
帰らない日々 抱きしめたまま
Embracing the days that won't return.
きっとそう きっと
Surely, yes, surely.
あの日の気持ち 受け止めないと
I have to accept the feelings of that day...
前に進むことができない
...or I can't move forward.
離したくない
I don't want to let go.
離れたくない
I don't want to be apart.
一つの願いは
My one wish is...
大好きだよと 伝えたいだけ
...just to tell you "I love you."
本当 素直じゃないけれど
Really, I'm not honest though.
So... How is it guys?
That was "Closing"... Do you take a lot of screenshot?
That was "Closing"... Do you take a lot of screenshots?
And ah! How about my new stage? Woah!
It's very cloudy here.
Yeah as you can see, there's two BIG CHEERS on the left and right.
みんな、どうだった？こぼのパフォーマンス。
How was it everyone? Kobo's performance.
いっぱいスクリーンショット撮れたかな？
Did you take lots of screenshots?
こぼの新しいステージはもうどうだった？かわいいでしょ？
How was Kobo's new stage? Cute, right?
ビッグ・チアーズがありますので、めっちゃかわいいよね。
There are Big Cheers, so it's super cute, isn't it?
So actually, yeah, we're already at the end of the show guys, but...
そろそろお別れ時間になりますよ。
It's about time to say goodbye.
But don't worry. Kobo still have something to share with you guys.
まだ皆さんにお知らせがあります。
I still have an announcement for everyone.
Jan jan ja-jan!
Ta-da!
Kobo Kanaeru Special Birthday 2025 Merch Set!
This time Kobo's birthday merch theme is... Jellyfish Princess...
I've wanted to wear a jellyfish costume for a long time...
And finally my wish came true!
So, how is it guys?
Do I look beautiful?
And the KV is drawn by Scotty-sensei.
スコッティ先生、ありがとう！
Scotty-sensei, thank you!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
And as you wish guys...
Finally! Jajan!
Finally! Ta-da!
Kobokers' Happi is here!
Now you guys can be proud Kobokers...
...and perfect for cheering me during events.
Keren banget.
It's so cool.
Happi, Happi, Happi.
Come on buy Happi, Happi!
And if you look closely...
...this Happi design is like... it's like my raincoat right?
And you can see...
...there's Tulululus in the front...
...and Me on the back.
Right?
And next!
We have this "Jellyfish Princess on the Wall" Tapestry!
It's printed with my brand new birthday illustration.
It's super high quality and perfect for decorating your wall.
You can wake up and see Kobo's smug face every morning.
And also, don't forget to praise the lord every day.
Then, look at this!
The "Jellyfish Princess, you got this" Button Badge Set!
Setto!
Set!
Two pieces.
One has my birthday outfit.
And the other is an illustration I drew by myself.
Yeah, by myself.
It looks good right?
Do you like it?
I drew it by myself.
So you can pin them to your bag...
...or your hat, or your heart.
Okay, so this one...
...is one of my favorites.
One, two, three...
Jajan!
Ta-da!
The Plushie Keychain!
It's me!
But mini Kobo in mini form.
You can bring me anywhere...
...on your backpack, your keys...
...your motorcycle...
...the car, whatever.
Even next to your computer while you watch my streams.
So soft and squishy.
And finally!
We also have the Situational Voice.
So it's called "Your One and Only Jellyfish Princess".
Ohhh what does it mean?
Buy it!
Buy it okay?
So you know what does it mean.
So you know what it means.
It is a special voice pack where I talk to you about Jellyfish Princess...
And you know, you're one and only just for you.
Don't miss out my birthday merch guys.
If you buy a set of them, you'll get a special bromide with my signature on it.
The merch is available for a limited time only.
So you can grab yours from the official shop.
Links are in the description.
So yeah, that's all for the announcement.
Thank you for coming and watching Kobo perform today.
以上、こぼからのお知らせでした。
That's all for the announcement from Kobo.
説明欄やチャット欄にリンクを貼ってありますので...
Links are in the description and chat...
...ポチっとしてね！
...so please click them!
But! I can hear some of you want an encore.
Encore?
アンコール欲しい？
Do you want an encore?
じゃあ、しょうがないなぁ。
Well, I guess I have no choice.
Please listen.
Sweet Memories.
懐かしい
It's a nostalgic...
痛みだわ
...pain.
ずっと前に
One I had forgotten...
忘れていた
...a long time ago.
でもあなたを見たとき
But the moment I saw you,
時間だけ
It was as if only time...
後戻りしたの
...had turned backwards.
「幸せ？」と聞かないで
Don't ask me if I'm happy.
嘘つくのは上手じゃない
I'm not very good at lying.
友達ならいるけど
I have friends, sure,
あんなには
But I just can't burn...
燃え上がれなくて
...with passion like that.
失った夢だけが
Only the dreams I've lost...
美しく見えるのは
...seem so beautiful now.
何故かしら
I wonder why?
過ぎ去った
Even the kindness...
優しさも今は
...that has passed is now...
甘い
...just a sweet...
記憶
...memory.
Sweet memories
キスしたらいけないわ
We shouldn't kiss.
傷をひとつ
It would only add...
増やすだけよ
...one more scar.
長い
For such a long...
間あなたに
...time, I missed you...
会いたくて
...and wanted to see you...
泣いていたくせに
...crying all the while.
あの頃は
Back then,
若すぎて
We were too young.
いたずらに
Needlessly...
傷つけあったふたり
...we hurt each other.
色褪せた
Even the faded...
悲しみも今は
...sadness is now...
遠い
...just a distant...
記憶
...memory.
Sweet memories
Woo...
La la la...
失った
Only the lost...
夢だけが
...dreams...
美しく
...seem so beautiful...
見えるのは何故かしら
...why is that, I wonder?
過ぎ去った
Even the kindness...
優しさも今は
...that has passed is now...
甘い
...just a sweet...
記憶
...memory.
Sweet memories
君は本当に
You really...
わかってない
...don't understand.
エンドより 甘くて豪華な
Sweeter and more luxurious than the end roll,
デザートより
More than dessert,
君がいいんだよ
I prefer you.
二つの傘より
Rather than two umbrellas,
相合い傘
sharing one together.
ちょっと冷たいけど
It's a little cold, but...
愛するための代償なら
If it's the price to pay for love,
いくらでもどうぞ
then take as much as you want.
ただずっとそばにいたい
I just want to stay by your side forever.
ねえ 誰を？星屑もんない
Hey, who? Stardust is boring.
二人ぼっちの世界でずっと
In a world of just us two, forever.
最後の花火を上げて
Launch the final fireworks,
フィナーレを飾って
decorate the finale,
奇跡の降る恋に落ちて
and fall in a love where miracles rain down.
誰も離さないで
Don't let anyone go.
味気ない世界も悪くないね
This dull world isn't so bad, is it?
どんなに恋をしたって
No matter how much I love,
出会えないよ きっと
I surely won't find another like this.
終わりのない幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss this never-ending happiness.
いつか今日を忘れても
Even if I forget today someday,
君がいいんだよ
it still has to be you.
天気雨の日 言い訳として
Using the sun shower as an excuse,
初めて目が合った
our eyes met for the first time.
ずっと覚えておくよ
I will remember it forever.
ねえ 誰を？星屑もんない
Hey, who? Stardust is boring.
二人ぼっちの世界でずっと
In a world of just us two, forever.
最後の花火を上げて
Launch the final fireworks,
フィナーレを飾って
decorate the finale,
奇跡の降る恋に落ちて
and fall in a love where miracles rain down.
誰も離さないで
Don't let anyone go.
味気ない世界も悪くないね
This dull world isn't so bad, is it?
どんなに恋をしたって
No matter how much I love,
忘れられないよ きっと
I surely won't be able to forget.
終わりのない幸せにキスをしよう
Let's kiss this never-ending happiness.
味気ないね
It's dull, isn't it?
でもそれがね
But that is,
二人の幸せ
our happiness together.
Oh my god, I almost cried.
I was crying in this song.
Thank you for today guys.
Thank you for watching until the end.
And thank you for Zeta-chan because she covered this Finale song first...
...and then I was inspired so yeah,
aku nyanyi di sini.
I sang it here.
いやいや、今日は来てくれて...
No, no, thank you for coming today...
今日は来てくれて、最後まで見てくれてありがとうございます。
Thank you for coming today, and thank you for watching until the very end.
I hope you guys enjoy all the performance.
Umm, yeah. This whole stream.
みんな大好き！
I love you all!
Thank you for your birthday wishes.
あとで読んであげますね。
I'll read them for you later, okay?
Bye bye minna! No more encore, no more encore. Bye bye!
Bye bye everyone! No more encore, no more encore. Bye bye!
Bokobokobo Kobo Kanaeru at your service.
Let me be your sun to shine your day.
Ehehe. Bye bye!
Thank you!
I can't be as bright as now without you!